I'm going to give Carrie here a nice neck massage.
But I'm going to use the pillow here for a little bit of her comfort, and my comfort.
So place the pillow behind the back, I'm going to come into an open diamond stance, knees on either side of our hips.
I'm going to have her tilt her head gently forward.
Intertwine my fingers, palms towards the neck, rest them on, and then start gently massaging as you pull the heels of the hands back.
And again, don't stay in one position; kind of go up and down a little bit, back and forth.
Try not to be too rough.
If you feel your client getting tense you know to back up just a little bit; ease up just a little bit, perfect.
Then after you do that you can give her a nice little massage with neck and shoulders.
So I'm going to just gently rub the neck, rub the shoulders.
Rub it out, give it a little loving kindness, and there you've got a neck massage.